https://healthy.net/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Healthy.net is owned and operated by HealthWorld Online.
HealthWorld Online is aware of the trust you place in us and our responsibility to protect your privacy. As part of this responsibility, we let you know what information we collect when you use our products and services, and why we collect it.
What We Collect and Where Do We Collect It
All users of http://www.healthy.net are free to explore most of the site without providing any personal information. If you want to access member-only areas, such as the discussion board and commenting on an article, or if you wish to receive our weekly newsletter, Healthy Update, you will be asked to provide your first and last name, email address and zip code.
How HealthWorld Online Uses This Information
a) Navigational: Our system automatically gathers information about the areas visited by users. To do this, HealthWorld Online logs IP addresses (in other words, the location of your computer on the Internet) for system administration, troubleshooting and to examine overall traffic trends. We do not use any of this navigational data on an individual basis. Nor do we share any of this data with outside companies. We do use navigational information in the aggregate to understand how our users travel around the site as a group to use the services that we of fer. We collect that information so that HealthWorld Online can constantly improve the site. We may also share this statistical information with our partners or other outside companies, but in doing so, we do not disclose individual names or personal navigational information.
b) Personal: When you place an order with any of HealthWorld Online’s Stores (www.healthyshopping.com) or products within Healthy.net, we will ask you for your name, address, phone, and email. In order to process the order. Additional information, such as your preferred means of payment and your shipping address, will be required. We might, from time to time, use the information provided to send you alerts about special offers and to create general customer profiles. You can “opt-out” of receiving such communication at any time, by unsubscribing to the email.
We Do Not Sell, Trade or Disclose Your Personal Information
HealthWorld Online does not disclose, share, sell or trade any personal or individual information that it collects to third parties other than in the course of completing a transaction that you have requested or in response to an investigation involving legal matters. While we may provide information regarding site usage to third parties, such as traffic reports and sale information, this information will not include any of your personal information.
HealthWorld Online Protects Customer Information
HealthWorld Online uses a secure server for any ordering and credit card information you provide. The servers use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an advanced encryption technology that safeguards your personal information and guarantees privacy. Our check-out process is certified secure and verified by GeoTrust (www.geotrust.com) and we are an Authorize.net certified merchant.
Please spread the word:Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)
arvindmishra007
View all posts
Get Our Weekly Healthy NewsletterWhat's your name? *First name only, please.And where should we send it? *Email addressPhoneSign me up
We Humbly Recommend
Top Posts & Pages
Where Does Love Go Wrong?, or The Three Demon Dialogues That Can Wreck Your Relationship
Enhancing your Immune System with Ayurveda
DHEA: When and How Much: Dosing Made Easy
I Cured My Glaucoma with Herbs
Use Psyllium – Instead of Metamucil
Explore MoreWellness Assessment
Shop
Read
Alternative Medicines
Experts
Invalid OAuth access token.
Wellness Assessment
Shop
Read
Alternative Medicines
Alternative Therapies
Aging Well
Conditions
Fitness
We Humbly Recommend
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we'll assume that you are happy with it.Ok
